# DAVID SELLAM

## FULLSTACK DEVELOPER REACT.JS, TYPESCRIPT

- C, C++, Java
- C#, PHP
- Ruby on Rails
- Javascript (ReactJS, NodeJS)
- Typescript
- Python

I am a fullstack developer and public speaker passionate about Typescript and React. For two years I taught people how to code at Le Wagon, while doing my BsC in Software Engineering, and working on client projects as a side hustle. I love learning new languages.

By night, I'm the Disco King of Tel Aviv.

#### CONTACT INFORMATION

- (972) 054-276-4061
- ✓ dvdsellam@gmail.com
- in LinkedIn: David Sellam
- https://github.com/dvd90

## EDUCATION BACKGROUND

### Shenkar College of Engineering and Design

BSC SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

• Top student in Web Development, 2020

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Fullstack developer (React team)

BATTATA.IO | 2019 - PRESENT

- Lead the development of web apps and digital tools, which includes working with and managing the needs of clients, developers, designers
- Worked closely in the planning and delivery of software products and services, including a New York based construction management platform that raised a \$2M investment by Disney
- Proficiency with MERN stack

#### Co-founder, Bootcamp Manager, Instructor

LE WAGON | 2018 - PRESENT

- Trained 120 entrepreneurs, product owners, and developers in 18 months
- Mentored students in designing and shipping to production over 70 tech products - 35 marketplaces and 35 web and mobile application
- Guest speaker at over 100 tech and coding lectures, including MTA Hackathon, IDC Adelson School of Entrepreneurship and weekly Le Wagon coding meetups

#### **Retention Manager**

PLAYTECH (MARKETS.COM) | 2013 - 2017

- Created economic reviews and market strategies to help clients achieve trading targets
- Built relationship with clients, cultivating a strong repeat customer base
- Trained new employees on product line and how to effectively "value add" and sell the brand

#### Le Wagon

FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM | 2018

 Designed, implemented and shipped to production a clone of AirBnB and a Rails prototype of ReadCoin (rdcn.io)